channelfilipino.net 2013-06-09

# Pinoy Channel TV - Privacy Policy

Your privacy matters to us.

**The types of information we collect:**

Channelfilipino.net collects the following types of information:

1\. Registration/contact information. When you register to watch videos on Channelfilipino.net, we collect your email address. We use this information to contact you for lost username or password purposes and to inform you about Site services in which you've expressed interest.

2\. Profile Information. Channelfilipino.net users have the ability to voluntarily create and modify their user profile using the " My Profile" menu. The information collected, such as name, age, sex and location is displayed to other users and is completely voluntary. Channelfilipino.net does not require users to create a user profile.

3\. No information specific to a user's personal identity is ever revealed unless the user “opts-in” to receive other specific information such as partner and advertiser offers.

4\. The information you supply to us when you are registering and setting up your personal Channelfilipino.net account is used to provide our basic services. Because we store your personal information, we don't have to ask you to re-register each time you want to access the site. Channelfilipino.net routinely sends all new members a welcoming email to verify their passwords and user names.

Channelfilipino.net may, at times, share aggregate statistical information about our members with business partners, sponsors and other affiliates. For example, we may share our findings that the Channelfilipino.net audience watches videos x hours per week. This information is aggregated and will not personally identify our members.

However, Channelfilipino.net may disclose personal information for the following business or legal reasons:

In special cases. When we have reason to believe, for example, that disclosing this information may help to identify, contact, or bring legal action against someone who, intentionally or unintentionally, may be causing injury or interference with Channelfilipino.net's rights or property, other Channelfilipino.net members, or anyone else who might be harmed as a result.

**Collection and use of members' IP addresses**

An IP address is a number that's automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the Web. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address.

Channelfilipino.net collects IP addresses to analyze trends, administer our site, anonymously track members' movements on our site, and to gather broad demographic information for statistical purposes. When guests request pages from the Site, our servers log those guests' IP addresses. We do not link IP addresses to any personal information, so that while a member's session will be logged, the member remains anonymous - to us, and to anyone else.

We use IP addresses in only a few types of situations. We may use these addresses to identify a member when it's necessary to enforce compliance with our policies or terms of service, or to protect our service, Site, customers or others. We may also use these addresses to capture time stamps so that we can determine peak and off-peak load times. These addresses may also be used to determine browser type for demographic information.

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp. 

**Your acceptance of this privacy policy**

By using the Site, you indicate your agreement with the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. If you do not agree with this privacy policy, then do not use the Site. We reserve the right to change the terms of this privacy policy. We will notify you of any material changes to this policy via email or by posting a prominent notice on the Site stating that the privacy policy has been updated. We will give you an opportunity to "opt out" of having your information collected and used pursuant to this materially different privacy policy. Also, we encourage you to review this privacy policy on a regular basis.
